Nevada Folklife Archive
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Photographs
  - Subseries 1: Slides, 8,390 still images (.jpg); 8,390 still images (.tif); 14,257 still images (.jpg); 14,257 still images (.tif)
    - Photos taken at the Thome house, Las Vegas, November 11, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-106; Lesley Williams; 4 color slides (35mm) (Box 52)
    - Photos taken at Dula Senior Center, Las Vegas. Bunku Shishu and Kogin embroidery by Yoko Arana, November 21, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-107; Lesley Williams; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 52)
    - Photos taken at Loretta Adams' home, Las Vegas, November 13, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-108 - S-1991-109; Lesley Williams; 26 color slides (35mm) (Box 52)
    - Navajo weaving, photos taken at Kim Ortiz's home, Las Vegas, November 14, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-110; Lesley Williams; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 52)
    - [Zoria Zetaruk pysansky], November 21, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-111; Lesley Williams; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 52)
    - Slides taken at Leonard Genes' home, Las Vegas, November 18, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-112 - S-1991-113; Lesley Williams; 21 color slides (35mm) (Box 52)
    - Slides taken at Maxine Mansor's house in Boulder City. Feltmaker, not traditional, November 19, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-114; Lesley Williams; 9 color slides (35mm) (Box 52)
    - Fern Adair Arts Center, Las Vegas, November 20, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-115; Lesley Williams; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 53)
    - Fern Adair Arts Center, Las Vegas, Wayne Panoke's hula dance class, November 20, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-116; Lesley Williams; 2 color slides (35mm) (Box 53)
    - [Barbara Glinski papercuts], November 17, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-117; Lesley Williams; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 53)
    - Slides taken at Carol Collins' home, Las Vegas (Painted Desert), Lois Mack's holiday preserve tasting, November 25, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-118; Lesley Williams; 7 color slides (35mm) (Box 53)
    - Slides taken at Samuel and Monique Johnson's home, Las Vegas, December 8, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-119; Lesley Williams; 2 color slides (35mm) (Box 53)
    - [Mark Willet bending glass], November 1, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-200; Russell Frank; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 53)
    - Don Beck, neon artist, November 5, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-201- S-1991-202; Russell Frank; 38 color slides (35mm) (Box 53)
    - Darwin's Magic Club, Las Vegas, November 6, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-203 - S-1991-205; Russell Frank; 48 color slides (35mm) (Box 53)
    - [Mike Sedeno bending glass], November 7, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-206; Russell Frank; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 53)
    - Saturday Bocce League, November 16, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-207; Russell Frank; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 53)
    - Italian American Club, exteriors, November 20, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-208; Russell Frank; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 53)
    - Woodcarver Roy DeVicente, November 24, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-209; Russell Frank; 13 color slides (35mm) (Box 53)
    - Main Street Station, Woodcarver Roy DeVicente, November 24, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-210; Russell Frank; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 53)
    - Gary Darwin's magic act at University of Nevada, Las Vegas magic class, November 25, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-211 - S-1991-212; Russell Frank; 37 color slides (35mm) (Box 54)
    - Temple Beth Shalom, Las Vegas, Hanukkah party, December 5, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-213; Russell Frank; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 54)
    - Georges LaForge, dessert maker, Savola Restaurant, Las Vegas, December 6, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-214; Russell Frank; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 54)
    - Jeff McColl, retired railroad man, December 6, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-215; Russell Frank; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 54)
    - Daniel Cros, magician, napkin sculptor, Ray Lectner, magician, December 9, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-216; Russell Frank; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 54)
    - Don Pablo Cigar Company, December 11, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-217 - S-1991-219; Russell Frank; 46 color slides (35mm) (Box 54)
    - Vic Jones, ceramicist, December 12, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-220 - S-1991-221; Russell Frank; 30 color slides (35mm) (Box 54)
    - Union Pacific Railroad yard, December 14, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-222; Russell Frank; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 54)
    - Patty Syms, glass engraver, December 15, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-223; Russell Frank; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 54)
    - Jose Gutierrez and Los Pregoneros del Puerto, Nevada State Museum and High School, March 30, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-224; Andrea Graham; 5 color slides (35mm) (Box 54)
    - Hawaiian crafts by Bernice Panahi Jarrett, February 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-001; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 54)
    - [Quilting], March 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-002; Andrea Graham; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 55)
    - FAA 1991-1992 Angie McGarva (master) and Tamea Knight (apprentice) Shoshone beadwork, April 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-003; Andrea Graham; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 55)
    - [Angie McGarva's beadwork], August 30, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-004; Andrea Graham; 19 color slides (35mm) (Box 55)
    - [Tammy Knight FAA 1991-1992], August 30, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-005; Andrea Graham; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 55)
    - FAA 1991-1992 Emma Bobb (master), Brenda Hooper and Jeanette Losh, September 1, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-006; Andrea Graham; 13 color slides (35mm) (Box 55)
    - Las Vegas International Food Festival, February 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-007; Andrea Graham; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 55)
    - Heart and Hand: Las Vegas Folk Crafts exhibit, Winchester Center, May 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-008 - S-1992-011; Andrea Graham; 72 color slides (35mm) (Box 55)
    - University of Nevada, Reno powwow, Reno, May 2, 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-012; Andrea Graham; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 55)
    - Baskets by Washoe artist Theresa Jackson, May 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-013; Andrea Graham; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 55)
    - Owyhee Junior Rodeo at Duck Valley Indian Reservation, July 4, 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-014; Andrea Graham; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 55)
    - Greek Food Festival, Sahara Hotel, Las Vegas, July 26, 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-015; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 55)
    - Las Vegas Hawaiian Festival, Lorenzi Park, September 12, 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-016; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 56)
    - Schurz Pine Nut Festival, September 19, 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-017 - S-1992-019; Andrea Graham; 48 color slides (35mm) (Box 56)
    - Adam Fortunate Eagle's carved stone pipes (1-10); Wa Pai Shone Nevada Day powwow in Carson City (11-17); Dean Barlese and the Red State Singers (15-17), September 1992 - October 31, 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-020; Andrea Graham; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 56)
    - Las Vegas survey, October 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-021; Andrea Graham; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 56)
    - Nevada Day powwow at Carson City, October 30, 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-022; Andrea Graham; 5 color slides (35mm) (Box 56)
    - Native American performances at Moapa High School, Overton, December 11, 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-023; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 56)
    - St. John's Greek Orthodox Church, folk dance groups rehearsal, December 12, 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-024 - S-1992-025; Andrea Graham; 33 color slides (35mm) (Box 56)
    - Christmas presentation by Philippine American Youth Organization (PAYO), Lied Discovery Children's Museum, December 13, 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-026 - S-1992-027; Andrea Graham; 30 color slides (35mm) (Box 56)
    - FAA 1992-1993, Aana Mitchell teaching a class in Hawaiian gourd crafts to members of the Las Vegas Hawaiian Civic Club, December 13, 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-028 - S-1992-030; Andrea Graham; 47 color slides (35mm) (Box 57)
    - FAA 1992-1993 master Aana Mitchell and Diane Ohata-Sims, December 14, 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-031 - S-1992-032; Andrea Graham; 37 color slides (35mm) (Box 57)
    - 1992 Folk Arts Gallery opening, 1992, AFC 2017/002: S-1992-033; Clark County Parks and Recreation; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 57)
    - Las Vegas Scots Pipe Band rehearsal, January 11, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-001; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 57)
    - Las Vegas Scots Pipe Band (1-4); Julia Samuels quilts at LXS in Carson City (5-8), January 11-16, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-002; Andrea Graham; 8 color slides (35mm) (Box 57)
    - Old Ties, New Attachments: Italian Folklife in the West exhibit at Nevada Museum of Art. Organized by American Folklife Center, Library of Congress, January 14, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-003; Andrea Graham; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 57)
    - Ballet Folklorico St. John's from Overton, rehearsing, February 8, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-004; Andrea Graham; 6 color slides (35mm) (Box 57)
    - Taiko drum class taught by Doug Muraoka, organized by Las Vegas Japanese American Citizen's League, February 9, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-005 - S-1993-006; Andrea Graham; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 57)
    - Taiko drum class taught by Doug Muraoka, organized by Las Vegas Japanese American Citizen's League, February 9, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-007; Andrea Graham; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 58)
    - Polish papercut artist Barbara Glinski, February 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-008; Andrea Graham; 10 color slides (35mm) (Box 58)
    - African American quilts (1-11); Washoe willow basketry (12-16), February 3, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-009; Andrea Graham; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 58)
    - FAA 1992-1993 Chippewa stone pipe carving. Master Adam Fortunate Eagle, apprentice Adam Tsosie Nordwall, also Jesse Windriver, March 28, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-010 - S-1993-011; Blanton Owen; 37 color slides (35mm) (Box 58)
    - Thai classical dance class taught by Pat Kanoknata, April 3, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-012 - S-1993-013; Andrea Graham; 39 color slides (35mm) (Box 58)
    - FAA 1992-1993 Washoe basketry. Master Theresa Jackson and apprentice Sue Coleman, April 17, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-014; Andrea Graham; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 58)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Native American drums and dancing, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-015 - S-1993-016; Blanton Owen; 37 color slides (35mm) (Box 58)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Filipino Flores de Mayo procession by Philippine American Youth Organization, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-017 - S-1993-018; Blanton Owen; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 58)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Poisonettes drill team, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-019; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 58)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Poisonettes drill team, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-020; Blanton Owen; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 59)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Thai Classical Dancers, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-021 - S-1993-022; Blanton Owen; 30 color slides (35mm) (Box 59)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Ethiopian Mutual Association of Nevada, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-023; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 59)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Ethiopian Mutual Association of Nevada (1-8); Amauta (9-14), May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-024; Blanton Owen; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 59)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Hawaiian dance, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-025; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 59)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Paraguayan music, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-026; Blanton Owen; 19 color slides (35mm) (Box 59)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Gospel music, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-027; Blanton Owen; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 59)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Warburton Family Bluegrass Band (9-18); St. John's Greek Orthodox Church Greek dancers (9-18), May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-028; Blanton Owen; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 59)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Caribbean music, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-029; Blanton Owen; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 59)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Gaming traditions, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-030; Blanton Owen; 19 color slides (35mm) (Box 59)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-031; Blanton Owen; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 59)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Magic, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-032; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 59)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Magic (1-10); Hidden Treasures exhibit (11-19), May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-033; Blanton Owen; 19 color slides (35mm) (Box 60)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-034 - S-1993-036; Blanton Owen; 54 color slides (35mm) (Box 60)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival. Navajo crafts, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-037 - S-1993-038; Blanton Owen; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 60)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-039 - S-1993-041; Blanton Owen; 54 color slides (35mm) (Box 60)
    - FAA 1992-1993 Powwow drumming (1-5); Las Vegas survey (exhibit) (6-9), May 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-042; Andrea Graham; 9 color slides (35mm) (Box 60)
    - Las Vegas survey (craft), May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-043; Andrea Graham; 12 color slides (35mm) (Box 60)
    - FAA 1993-1994, Pat Kanoknata (master) and Sanantha Lopez (apprentice), September 12, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-044; Andrea Graham; 8 color slides (35mm) (Box 60)
    - FAA 1993-1994, Amy Barber (master) and Jody Steele (apprentice), August 26, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-045; Andrea Graham; 13 color slides (35mm) (Box 60)
    - FAA 1993-1994, Evelyn Pete (master) and Edna Mike (apprentice), October 16, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-046; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 60)
    - FAA 1993-1994, Evelyn Pete (master) and Edna Mike (apprentice), October 16, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-047 - S-1993-049; Andrea Graham; 57 color slides (35mm) (Box 61)
    - FAA 1993-1994 Thai Classical Dance, Pat Kanoknata (master) and Santhana Lopez (apprentice), Thai dance class at Reed-Whipple Cultural Center, December 5, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-050 - S-1993-051; Andrea Graham; 32 color slides (35mm) (Box 61)
    - FAA 1993-1994 Ukrainian Pysanky. Zoria Zetaruk (master) with Luba Eads and Natalie Pruc (apprentices);, December 6, 1993, AFC 2017/002: S-1993-052 - S-1994-001; Andrea Graham; 31 color slides (35mm) (Box 61)
    - D Bar J Hat Company, Las Vegas, March 3, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-002; Andrea Graham; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 61)
    - Asian Pacific Americans of Northern Nevada Luau, Lawlor Events Center, Reno, March 12, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-003; Andrea Graham; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 61)
    - FAA 1993-1994, Master Evelyn Pete and apprentice Edna Mike, Shoshone willow baskets, Duckwater (1-12); FAA 1993-1994, Oscar Carrescia (master) teaching Argentinean guitar to Olga Carbia, Las Vegas (13-16), March 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-004; Andrea Graham; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 61)
    - Kids on Stage, performances at Sierra Arts Foundation, Reno, April 9, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-005 - S-1994-007; Andrea Graham; 42 color slides (35mm) (Box 61)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, April 24, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-008; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 61)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, April 24, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-009 - S-1994-017; Andrea Graham; 170 color slides (35mm) (Box 62)
    - Asian Pacific Festival of Fortune, Victorian Square, Sparks (1-15); FAA 1993-1994, Jody Steele, apprentice in Washoe basketry with her grandmother Amy Barber (16-20), May 21, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-018-; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 62)
    - Reno Basque Festival, Victorian Square, Sparks, August 20, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-019- S-1994-020; Andrea Graham; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 62)
    - Fernley Rodeo, October 2, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-021; Eliza Buck; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 63)
    - Fernley Rodeo (1-6); Tongan Methodist Congregation (5-14), October 2, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-022; Eliza Buck; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 63)
    - Interfaith Gospel Choir practice at the Second Baptist Church, October 3, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-023 - S-1994-024; Eliza Buck; 37 color slides (35mm) (Box 63)
    - Dan Price, silversmith, bit and spur maker, cowboy, manages Green Gulch Ranch, October 4, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-025; Eliza Buck; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 63)
    - The Magic Shop, magicians Terry Wilson and Don Brandfes, October 5, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-026; Eliza Buck; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 63)
    - Visha Siddharthan teaching Bharata Natya (South Indian dance) at home in Sparks, October 7, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-027; Eliza Buck; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 63)
    - Visha Siddharthan teaching Bharata Natya (South Indian dance) at home in Sparks (1-8); Flutter the clown (9-17), October 7, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-028; Eliza Buck; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 63)
    - FAAN (Filipino American Association of Nevada) Dancers at University Nevada, Reno event, October 3, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-029; Eliza Buck; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 63)
    - Lightning William auctioning cars, October 8, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-030; Eliza Buck; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 63)
    - Columbus Parade and Italian Festival, October 8, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-031; Eliza Buck; 19 color slides (35mm) (Box 63)
    - Local Native American basketry in Wade's silver shop (1-7); miscellaneous images from Hispanic community (8-12), October 8, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-032; Eliza Buck; 12 color slides (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Navaratri Festival at SAF (Sierra Arts Foundation), October 8, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-033; Eliza Buck; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 64)
    - AME Church elder choir singing at Sunday service (1-3); H.B. McCay standing with great-uncle's saddle (4-5); saddle seen in Bronco to Breakfast painting (6); H.B. McCay standing with his show saddle (7-8); standing at gate (9-10); preparing to shoe a horse (11-13); unknown (14-19), October 9, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-034; Eliza Buck; 19 color slides (35mm) (Box 64)
    - H.B. McCay shoeing horse's front hooves (1-12); cleaning horse's back hooves (13-15), October 9, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-035; Eliza Buck; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Tongan Congregation Dance and Choir practice at the home of lay minister in Sparks, October 10, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-036; Eliza Buck; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Tongan Congregation Dance and Choir practice at the home of lay minister in Sparks (1-7); Colin Sendall demonstrating water dowsing techniques (8-16), October 10, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-037; Eliza Buck; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Dolores Burnett teaching children folkloric dances at Essex Manor (1-12); Manuel Ramirez Hernandez singing to restaurant guests (13-14); singing traditional songs (15-20), October 13, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-038; Eliza Buck; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Manuel Ramirez Hernandez singing traditional songs (1-3); musician (4); Puja altar in Hindu home of Arun Sachdev (5-7); Hindu god Shiva in home of Arun Sachdev (8); Karen Burns (showgirl and show producer) in Reno home (9); looking at different showgirl costumes (10-16); unknown (17), October 13, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-039; Eliza Buck; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Nancy and Crystal Jackson, hair preparation for braiding (1-4); Nancy waving Crystal's hair (5-7); Nancy braiding in hair extension using fishbone style (8-11); Nancy crimping own hair (from weave) (12); Nancy holding grandmother's curling iron (13); Nancy pointing (14); unknown (15), October 15, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-040; Eliza Buck; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Norm and Bernie DeLorme showing family baskets and gambling games, October 16, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-041; Eliza Buck; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Norm [DeLorme] showing family baskets and gambling games (1-4); Indian market (5-10); The Steeles-circus trapeze flyers (11-20), October 16, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-042; Eliza Buck; 19 color slides (35mm) (Box 65)
    - Lawrence Lopes in front yard with yard art, October 17, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-043; Eliza Buck; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 65)
    - Celtic New Year celebration, November 5, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-044 - S-1994-046; Tamara Layman; 55 color slides (35mm) (Box 65)
    - Second Baptist Church Service and Gospel music, Diwali Festival sponsored by the IANN (India Association of Northern Nevada) at Billinghurst Middle School, November 5, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-047 - S-1994-048; Tamara Layman; 37 color slides (35mm) (Box 65)
    - Reno Basque Festival, Victorian Square, Sparks, Elko Basque Dancers performing, August 20, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-049; Andrea Graham; 13 color slides (35mm) (Box 65)
    - Owyhee Labor Day Indian Rodeo, September 4, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-050; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 65)
    - Owyhee Labor Day Indian Rodeo (1-9); Reno Greek Festival (10-20), September 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-051; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 65)
    - FAA 1995, Las Vegas Japanese American Citizens League Kaminari Taiko Drummers practice. Clark High School. Doug Muraoka (master) William Fujii and Norma Wagoner (apprentices), September 21, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-052; Andrea Graham; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 66)
    - FAA 1995 Saddlemaking. Eddie Brooks (master) and Alan McDonald (apprentice), September 28, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-053; Andrea Graham; 9 color slides (35mm) (Box 66)
    - FAA 1995 buckskin tanning. Edward McDade (master) with Lyle Sam (apprentice), September 29, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-054; Andrea Graham; 13 color slides (35mm) (Box 66)
    - Snow Dance Festival, Lake Tahoe, October 1, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-055; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 66)
    - FAA 1995 apprenticeship in African drumming, Mohammed Barrie (master) and Eric Jackson (apprentice), October 26, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-056; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 66)
    - FAA 1995 apprenticeship in African drumming, Mohammed Barrie (master) and Eric Jackson (apprentice) (1-4); Reno Celtic Festival (4-20), October 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-057; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 66)
    - FAA 1995 African drumming and Taiko drumming, cultural exchange between African and Japanese drumming apprenticeships, performance by Taiko group, November 16, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-058 - S-1994-060; Andrea Graham; 54 color slides (35mm) (Box 66)
    - Reno Japanese American Citizens League annual mochi making party, November 20, 1994, AFC 2017/002: S-1994-061 - S-1994-062; Andrea Graham; 38 color slides (35mm) (Box 66)
    - 1994-1995 Apprenticeship in Shoshone willow basketry. At Lilly's house in Fallon, Lilly Sanchez (master), Virginia Sanchez (apprentice), January 14, 1995, AFC 2017/002: S-1995-001; Andrea Graham; 9 color slides (35mm) (Box 66)
    - FAA 1994-1995 Apprenticeship in buckskin tanning. Edward McDade (master), Lyle Sam (apprentice). Ed and Lyle smoking a hide, and scraping hides at Ed's place in Lee, January 22, 1995, AFC 2017/002: S-1995-002; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 66)
    - FAA 1994-1995 Apprenticeship in buckskin tanning. Edward McDade (master), Lyle Sam (apprentice). Ed and Lyle smoking a hide, and scraping hides at Ed's place in Lee, January 22, 1995, AFC 2017/002: S-1995-003; Andrea Graham; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 67)
    - Cooking demonstration (Shoshone) at Cowboy Poetry Gathering, January 1995, AFC 2017/002: S-1995-004; Andrea Graham; 9 color slides (35mm) (Box 67)
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, school program, April 21, 1995, AFC 2017/002: S-1995-005 - S-1995-009; Andrea Graham; 98 color slides (35mm) (Box 67)